README.md 4/3/2022

Nazmul Hudha

Technologies | Projects | Experience | Education |Interests | Contact

Introduction

I am an adaptable and reliable **Frontend React Developer**, with lots of previous experience working with company tools and technologies; now looking for a position on the development team.

After having worked on the sales side of digital products for a number of years within Tech companies; I realised it is programming and solving problems that I enjoy more. So I am excited, to use my digital technical skills to to help turn ideas into innovative new features, products & services.

I would describe myself as someone who is open minded, a good learner (self-taught Japanese then lived in Japan for 2 years), and can easily get along well with different types of people.

Technologies

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Libraries & Frameworks: React, Bootstrap, Tailwind, SASS

Tools & Methodologies: Git, NPM, web API's (incl. JSON & AJAX), Agile Development

Projects

Name	Description	Tech/tools	Source Code
Portfolio-Web- Build	A responsive, Personal Portfolio Site Build	HTML, CSS, Javascript	Portfolio Site
Miracle Shoe	Team Build, Frontend Shoe E- Commerce site	React, NPM packages	Miracle Shoe
NES-CSS- Dialogue	Using NESS CSS framework	NESS CSS, NPM packages	Ness Css
React App1	React App one	TBC	React App1
React App2	React App two	TBC	React App2

Other Mini Builds

- Random-Color-Generator JS App | Color-Generator
- Pokemon-Sprite JS Build | Pokemon-Sprite
- Photo-Slideshow-Web JS Build | Photo-slideshow
- Number Guessing-Game JS App | number-guesser

Experience

README.md 4/3/2022

Bath Spa University (Jan 2022 - April 2022)

Web Development Coding Bootcamp

 Worked with technologies including: React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node.JS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, NPM packages

- Agile Development Methodology
- Pair programming and final team build project

POWREADY (Oct 2020 - Present)

Sales Manager

- Design and implement a strategic sales plan to help expand Powready's products, services and help grow its UK customer base
- Developing the sales process, achieving growth, meeting planned quarterly sales targets and managing a growing sales team
- Forecast & budget sales revenue, as well as in charge of expansion, retention and churns

Receipt Bank (Feb 2020 - Aug 2020)

Account Development Manager

- Taking a consultative approach to form long-term partnerships with clients and businesses; assisting them in streamlining, growing and future-proofing their accountancy firms
- Manage, develop and nurture relationships with key stakeholders and strategic partners at all levels on either side of the upsell in order to maximise revenue and growth

Uber (Nov 2018 - May 2019)

Virtual Restaurant Account Manager

- Build & maintain relationships with stakeholders at UberEats top 10% of best performing restaurants
 & brands across the UK
- Using UberEats Data to find market selection gaps; identify and initiate new partnership opportunities; and pitching & closing new exclusive brands, owning the entire end-to-end sales process
- Working & communicating with teams around the globe; building a Sales Playbook to train future sales team

Restaurant Partnership Account Executive

- Own the restaurant selection by launching Uber Eats into new cities, towns and territories across the UK
- Driving Revenue and effectively managing a sales pipeline, with different sales cycles and timelines across UK cities
- Finding and qualifying leads, negotiating terms and closing deals, owning the entire end-to-end sales process

Lewisham Council (Feb 2018 - Nov 2018)

Commercial Sales Territory Account Manager

Samsung Electronics (April 2017 - Dec 2017)

Customer Service Team Lead

README.md 4/3/2022

Huntress Group (June 2016 - Feb 2017)

Accounting & Finance Recruitment Consultant

Japan Exchange and Teaching Program (JET) (Aug 2014 - May 2016)

English Language Teacher

Education

Bath Spa University (Jan 2022 - April 2022) Web Development Bootcamp

SOAS University of London & King's College London (2009 - 2014) BA Arabic & Geography (Joint Honours)

• Final Project: Geography City Planning Essay Written in Arabic

Interests

Languages

- English (Native)
- Japanese (Conversational)

Hobbies

• Taekwondo (won Gold at British Masters)

Contact

• Github: nazhudha

• Linkedin: Nazmul Hudha